bigfuck.tv 2019-08-02

# Privacy Policy

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on BigFuck.TV. The security of your Data is very important to BigFuck.TV and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

## DATA COLLECTED

Principles of using cookies by the website BigFuck.TV

When you visit some internet resource, it sends a little text file to your PC. Information in this file may assist the website to store some data about your behavior for the future, for example, the quality of the video which you prefer to watch or some other settings. These files are of high importance. The World Wide Web wouldn’t be such a comfortable place, if there would be no cookies.

You can review the cookies utilized by BigFuck.TV, and also figure out how BigFuck.TV and our partners use such data in the business. You can review Data Protection Guidelines of our website to understand how we ensure your protection when utilizing cookies and some other data.

## How you can manage cookies

Optionally, you can manage and erase [cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). If you are interested in more information, please refer to website aboutcookies.org. You are able to erase all cookies from any device and also you are able to cancel the saving of such files in almost every internet browser. In such event, please note that you probably will have to change some specific settings while you are visiting website and also some features of the website won’t function in a normal course.

Here is a list of companies which store the data on our behalf and use cookies:

## Google Analytics

Terms of Service: <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html>

Privacy Statement: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html>

Privacy Policy: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>

## Personal Information:

Users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed.

Cookies: When you visit BigFuck.TV, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. BigFuck.TV uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.

Log File Information: When you visit BigFuck.TV, our servers may record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

## USES

We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the BigFuck.TV user-experience.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

If under duty to do so BigFuck.TV may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of BigFuck.TV or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is BigFuck.TV's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.

Should you deliberately upload any illegal material BigFuck.TV shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

## YOUR RIGHTS

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section. If you have additional questions then please contact us.
